Website Privacy Policy Cambiumlearning.com
------------------------------------------

* * *

Last reviewed: November 4, 2020 

Last updated and effective as of: November 4, 2020

Cambium Intermediate Holdings LLC., (also referred to as “the Company,” “We,” “Us” or “Our” in this policy), is the parent company and owner of multiple operating companies (referred to herein individually and collectively as “Brands”), each of which offers and provides various digital and blended curriculum, professional learning, assessments, and other educational and instructional products, services and resources, that are designed to support and drive proficiency, equity, and improved learning outcomes in classrooms everywhere.

[www.cambiumlearning.com](https://www.cambiumlearning.com/) (the “Website”) and when You interact with Us or use any content, resources or services on the Website. This Privacy Policy also tells You about Your privacy rights and protections afforded to You.

For the privacy policies concerning how each Brand collects and uses personal information of visitors to their Brand websites, or concerning the collection and use by each Brand of personal information of school or district students, staff or other users that is collected within and through use of the online and off-line products and services offered by that Brand, please refer to the privacy policies available from each Brand.

As described in this Privacy Policy, We use Your Personal data to provide and improve the Service. By visiting Our Website or using the Service, You agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy as it may change at any time at our sole discretion. Our Website contains links to the individual Brand site(s), and/or to third party sites, that are not subject to this Privacy Policy. The content and privacy policies and practices of those sites are the responsibility of those sites; We recommend that You read the privacy policy of any such sites that You visit.

### Interpretation and Definitions

**Interpretation** 

The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions. The following definitions shall have the same meaning regardless of whether they appear in singular or in plural.

**Definitions**

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy:

**Account** means a unique account created for You to access our Service or parts of our Service.

**Business**, for the purpose of the CCPA (California Consumer Privacy Act), refers to the Company as the legal entity that collects California Consumers' personal information and determines the purposes and means of the processing of Consumers' personal information, or on behalf of which such information is collected and that alone, or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of consumers' personal information, that does business in the State of California.

**Company** (referred to as either "the Company", "We", "Us" or "Our" in this Policy) refers to Cambium Intermediate Holdings LLC., 17855 Dallas Parkway, Suite 400, Dallas, Texas 75287.

For the purpose of the GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation), the Company is the Data Controller of Personal Data processed under this Privacy Policy.

**Consumer**, for the purpose of the CCPA (California Consumer Privacy Act), means a natural person who is a California resident. A resident, as defined in the law, includes (1) every individual who is in the USA for other than a temporary or transitory purpose, and (2) every individual who is domiciled in the USA who is outside the USA for a temporary or transitory purpose.

**Cookies** are small files that are placed on Your computer, mobile device or any other device by a website, containing the details of Your browsing history on that website among its many uses.

**Data Controller**, for the purposes of the GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation), refers to the Company as the legal entity which alone or jointly with others determines the purposes and means of the processing of Personal Data.

**Device** means any device that can access the Service such as a computer, a cellphone or a digital tablet.

**Do Not Track** (DNT) is a concept that has been promoted by US regulatory authorities, in particular the U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC), for the Internet industry to develop and implement a mechanism for allowing internet users to control the tracking of their online activities across websites.

**Personal Data** is any information that relates to an identified or identifiable individual.

For the purposes of the GDPR, Personal Data means any information relating to a Data Subject under the GDPR, such as a name, an identification number, location data, online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity.

For the purposes of the CCPA, Personal Data means any information that identifies, relates to, describes or is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a California Consumer.

**Sale**, for the purpose of the CCPA (California Consumer Privacy Act), means selling, renting, releasing, disclosing, disseminating, making available, transferring, or otherwise communicating orally, in writing, or by electronic or other means, a California Consumer's Personal Data to another business or a third party for monetary or other valuable consideration.

**Service** refers to the Website.

**Service Provider** means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Company. It refers to third-party companies or individuals employed by the Company to facilitate the Service, to provide the Service on behalf of the Company, to perform services related to the Service or to assist the Company in analyzing how the Service is used. For the purpose of the GDPR, Service Providers are considered Data Processors.

**Third-party Social Media Service** refers to any website or any social network website through which a User can log in or create an account to use the Service.

**Usage Data** refers to data collected automatically, either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).

**Website** refers to [www.cambiumlearning.com](https://www.cambiumlearning.com/)

**You** means the individual accessing or using the Service, or the company, or other legal entity on behalf of which such individual is accessing or using the Service, as applicable.

Under GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation), You can be referred to as the Data Subject or as the User as you are the individual using the Service.

### Collecting and Using Your Personal Data 

**Types of Data Collected** 

**Personal Data:** While using Our Service, We may collect or ask You to provide Us with certain Personal Data that could be used to contact or identify You. Personal Data we may collect may include, but is not limited to:

Email address

First name and last name

Job Title

Company name

Personal or professional contact and address information

Mobile telephone number

Payment details and/or transaction history

Usage Data

**Usage Data:** Usage Data is collected automatically when using the Service.

Usage Data may include information such as Your Device's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that You visit, the time and date of Your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

When You access the Service by or through a mobile device, We may collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device You use, Your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of Your mobile device, Your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser You use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

We may also collect information that Your browser sends whenever You visit our Service or when You access the Service by or through a mobile device.

**Tracking Technologies and Cookies**

We use Cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on Our Service and store certain information. Tracking technologies used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze Our Service. The technologies We use may include:

**Cookies or Browser Cookies.** A cookie is a small file placed on Your Device. You can instruct Your browser to refuse all Cookies or to indicate when a Cookie is being sent. However, if You do not accept Cookies, You may not be able to use some parts of our Service. Unless you have adjusted Your browser setting so that it will refuse Cookies, our Service may use Cookies.

**Flash Cookies.** Certain features of our Service may use local stored objects (or Flash Cookies) to collect and store information about Your preferences or Your activity on our Service. Flash Cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as those used for Browser Cookies. For more information on how You can delete Flash Cookies, please read "Where can I change the settings for disabling, or deleting local shared objects?" available at [helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html#main\_Where\_can\_I\_change\_the\_settings\_for\_disabling\_\_or\_deleting\_local\_shared\_objects\_](https://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html#main_Where_can_I_change_the_settings_for_disabling__or_deleting_local_shared_objects_)

**Web Beacons.** Certain sections of our Service and our emails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of a certain section and verifying system and server integrity).

Cookies can be "Persistent" or "Session" Cookies. Persistent Cookies remain on Your personal computer or mobile device when You go offline, while Session Cookies are deleted as soon as You close Your web browser. Learn more about cookies: [What Are Cookies?](https://www.privacypolicies.com/blog/cookies/).

We use both Session and Persistent Cookies for the purposes set out below:

**Necessary / Essential Cookies**

Type: Session Cookies

Administered by: Us

Purpose: These Cookies are essential to provide You with services available through the Website and to enable You to use some of its features. They help to authenticate users and identify and prevent fraudulent use of user accounts and traffic to the Website. Without these Cookies, services that we provide from Our Website or that You have asked for cannot be provided, and We only use these Cookies to provide You with those services.

**Cookies Policy / Notice Acceptance Cookies**

Type: Persistent Cookies

Administered by: Us

Purpose: These Cookies identify if users have accepted the use of cookies on the Website.

**Functionality Cookies**

Type: Persistent Cookies

Administered by: Us

Purpose: These Cookies allow us to remember choices You make when You use the Website, such as remembering your login details or language preference. The purpose of these Cookies is to provide You with a more personal experience and to avoid You having to re-enter your preferences every time You use the Website.

**Tracking and Performance Cookies**

Type: Persistent Cookies

Administered by: Third-Parties

Purpose: These Cookies are used to track information about traffic to the Website and how users use the Website. The information gathered via these Cookies may directly or indirectly identify you as an individual visitor. This is because the information collected is typically linked to a pseudonymous identifier associated with the device you use to access the Website. We may also use these Cookies to test new pages, features or new functionality of the Website to see how our users react to them.

If you do not want to help Us learn how to improve our Website, services and strategies for marketing and outreach, etc., you may choose to set your Web browser to not accept certain cookies. You can control the use of certain cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on Our Website. Further information on how to prevent cookies from being stored on your computer can be found on  [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) under the ‘manage cookies’ section. Alternatively, go to the help menu within your Internet browser.

From time to time we may engage and permit third party companies to set cookies on the Website for purposes which may include market research or to help us to analyze and improve functionality of the Website. We may also, from time to time, utilize cookies or other tracking devices, and work with third party advertising companies that utilize their own cookies or similar technologies, that will interact with or recognize technology on your browser or device when you visit Our Website, for purposes of serving you targeted and customized advertising (also referred to as “remarketing” or "online behavioral advertising") about Our Website and services, as you browse the Internet. As noted above, you can set your device or browser to accept or reject most cookies, or at least notify you in most situations that the technology is offered. As an additional step, these advertising companies may participate in one of the following self-regulatory programs for online behavioral advertising, with corresponding user opt-outs:

* Networking Advertising Initiative ([www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)) (US Only)
* Digital Advertising Alliance ([www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/)) (US Only)
* European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance ([www.youronlinechoices.eu/](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)) (EU Only)
* Digital Advertising Alliance - Canada ([youradchoices.ca/choices](http://youradchoices.ca/choices)) (Canada Only)
* DAA App Choices Mobile App (Mobile Devices Only) - For mobile devices (e.g., smartphone, tablets), you may consider downloading the DAA AppChoices Mobile App to manage such technology. Your mobile device may give You the ability to opt out of the use of information about the apps You use in order to serve You ads that are targeted to Your interests:
* "Opt out of Interest-Based Ads" or "Opt out of Ads Personalization" on Android devices
* "Limit Ad Tracking" on iOS devices

You can also stop the collection of location information from Your mobile device by changing the preferences on Your mobile device.

**Specific Cookies and Tracking Technologies:**

**Analytics** 

**Google Analytics**

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

**Remarketing** 

**Google Ads (AdWords)**

Google Ads (AdWords) remarketing service is provided by Google Inc.

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customise the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: [www.google.com/settings/ads](http://www.google.com/settings/ads)

Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on - [tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) - for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.

**Using Performance and Miscellaneous** 

**Invisible reCAPTCHA**

We use an invisible captcha service named reCAPTCHA. reCAPTCHA is operated by Google.

The reCAPTCHA service may collect information from You and from Your Device for security purposes.

The information gathered by reCAPTCHA is held in accordance with the Privacy Policy of Google: [www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

**FreshDesk**

FreshDesk is a customer support software. The service is operated by Freshworks, Inc.

FreshDesk service may collect information from Your Device.

The information gathered by FreshDesk is held in accordance with its Privacy Policy: [www.freshworks.com/privacy/](https://www.freshworks.com/privacy/)

Please note that even if you reject such technology, you may continue to receive advertisements, but the advertisements will not be tailored to your browsing activities and interests.

**Use of Your Personal Data** 

The Company may use Personal Data for the following purposes:

To provide and maintain our Service, including to monitor the usage of our Service, troubleshoot problems, protect against fraud or misuse, or resolve complaints or disputes.

To manage Your Account: to manage Your registration as a user of the Service. To the extent account creation is made available on the Website, the Personal Data You provide can give You access to different functionalities of the Service that are available to You as a registered user.

For the performance of a contract: To the extent the ability to enter into purchase transactions is made available from the Website, the Personal Data You provide may be used for the development, compliance and undertaking of the purchase contract for the products, items or services You have purchased from this Website or of any other contract with Us from the Website.

To contact You: To contact You by email, telephone calls, SMS, or other equivalent forms of electronic communication, such as a mobile application's push notifications regarding updates or informative communications related to the functionalities, products or services, including the security updates, when necessary or reasonable for their implementation.

To provide You with news, special offers and general information about Our Company and events, including news and general information about any of our Brands and any goods, services and events which we or the Brands offer that are similar to those that You have already purchased or inquired about, unless You have opted not to receive such information from Us. You may update Your email preferences at any time by using the “unsubscribe” link found in emails We send to you or by contacting us at  [privacy@cambiumlearning.com](mailto:privacy@cambiumlearning.com).

To manage Your requests: To attend and manage Your inquiries and requests to Us.

To deliver targeted advertising to You: We may use Your information to develop and display content and advertising (and work with third-party vendors who do so) tailored to Your interests and/or location and to measure its effectiveness.

For business transfers: We may use Your Personal Data to evaluate or conduct a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which Personal Data held by Us about our Service users is among the assets transferred.

For other purposes: We may use Your Personal Data for other purposes, such as data analysis, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns and to evaluate and improve our Service, products, services, marketing and your experience.

### Sharing, Transfer and Disclosure of Your Personal Data 

We may share Your Personal Data in the following situations:

* **With Service Providers:** We may share Your Personal Data with Service Providers we contract with to monitor and analyze the use of Our Service, to advertise on third party websites to You after You visited our Service, or to contact You about Our Services.
* **For business transfers:** We may share or transfer Your Personal Data in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of Our Company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of Our Company business to another company.
* **With Affiliates:** We may share Your Personal Data with Our affiliates, in which case We will require those affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy with respect to Your Personal Data unless and until You have accepted their Privacy Policy. Affiliates include Our parent company and any other subsidiaries, joint venture partners or other companies that We control or that are under common control with Us.
* **With business partners:** We may share Your Personal Data with Our business partners as provided herein to offer You certain products, services or promotions.
* **With other users:** when You share Your Personal Data or otherwise interact with other users in any public or interactive areas that may be made available on the Website, such information may be viewed by all users and may be publicly distributed outside. If You interact with other users or register through a Third-Party Social Media Service, Your contacts on the Third-Party Social Media Service may see Your name, profile, pictures and description of Your activity, and other users may be able to view descriptions of Your activity, communicate with You and view Your profile.
* **With Law Enforcement or Regulatory Authorities:** Under certain circumstances, the Company may be required to disclose Your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency), including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements..
* **For other Legal purposes:** The Company may disclose Your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

Comply with a legal, regulatory or contractual obligation

Protect and defend the rights or property of the Company

Prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service

Protect the personal safety of Users of the Service or the public

Protect against legal liability

* **With Your consent**: We may disclose Your Personal Data for other purposes with Your consent.

**Transfer of Your Personal Data**

The Internet is a global environment. Websites, software, services and programs delivered and accessed through the Internet necessarily involve the transmission and processing of personal data, sometimes on an international basis, depending, for example, on where the visitor or user is located. When Personal Data is provided to Us through the Website, the information will be processed from and stored on servers located in the United States and globally, and by using the Website, you acknowledge and give Us authorization to such transfer, processing and storage.

The Company is committed to taking all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that Your Personal Data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the requirements of applicable law.

**Retention of Your Personal Data** 

The Company will retain Your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use Your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

The Company will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of Our Service, or We are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

**Security of Your Personal Data** 

The security of Your Personal Data is important to Us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, and no website or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While We strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect Your Personal Data, We cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Access to Personal Data & Request Process**

Upon written request and as provided herein, We will provide You with information about whether We hold any of Your Personal Data. You may access, correct, or request deletion of Your Personal Data under this Privacy Policy by contacting Us as provided herein. We will respond to Your request within a reasonable timeframe.

**GDPR**

Where required by applicable law, and notably by the **General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)** for residents of the UK and European Union, You have the right to obtain confirmation of the existence of certain Personal Data relating to You, to verify its content, origin, and accuracy, as well as the right to access, review, port, delete, or to block or withdraw consent to the processing of certain Personal Data (without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal), by contacting Us as detailed below. **In particular, You have the right to object to Our use of Your Personal Data for any direct marketing and in certain other situations at any time**. Please note that certain Personal Data may be retained as required or permitted by applicable law.

If You are a resident of the UK or European Union with questions regarding Your rights in Personal Data under GDPR, You may contact us at:  [privacy@cambiumlearning.com](mailto:privacy@cambiumlearning.com).

We may charge the allowable fee under applicable law for provision of this information. We will respond to Your request within a reasonable timeframe. Please note that additional information may be required to confirm and enable Us to assist with Your request. The timeframe to address the request may vary depending on the nature of the request, however, We will endeavor to address the request as promptly as possible, typically within thirty (30) days and as may be required by law.

You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about Our collection and use of Your Personal Data. For more information, if You are in the European Economic Area (EEA), please contact Your local data protection authority in the EEA.

### CCPA Privacy Notice

**_Notice to California Consumers_**

If You are a Consumer and reside in California, We are required to provide additional information to You about how We use and disclose Your information, and You may have additional rights with regard to how We use Your information. We have included this California-specific information below.

* **CA Personal Information**. Consistent with **_Types of Data Collected_** Section of this **_Privacy Policy_**, We collect or may collect certain categories and specific pieces of information about individuals that are considered "Personal Information" in California under CCPA ("**CA Personal Information**"), specifically:
    * **_Personal and Other Identifiers or Characteristics_**: _such as first name and last name, personal or professional contacting information, mailing address, telephone number, e-mail address, unique personal identifier, IP, device, and online activity information, age, date of birth, gender, demographics, username and password to our Website or services;_
    * _**_Commercial Information_**_: such as payment details, credit card information and purchase or transaction history;__
    * **_Sources_**_._ We may collect certain categories of CA Personal Information from You and other third parties as described in the **_Tracking Technologies and Cookies_** Section and the **_Sharing, Transfer and Disclosure of Your Personal Data_** Section of this _**Privacy Policy**._
* _**Use of CA Personal Information**_._ Consistent with the **_Use of Your Personal Data_** Section of this **_Privacy Policy_**_,_ We may use CA Personal Information for business or commercial purposes. Please see the **_Use of Your Personal Data_** Section of this Privacy Policy for more details_._  
    _
* **CA Personal Information Sold or Disclosed For Business Purposes.**
    * In the preceding twelve months, We may have shared CA Personal Information for business purposes, or We may have “sold” (as defined under CCPA) some categories of CA Personal Information.
* **California Consumer Rights**. Subject to certain exceptions, as a California resident and Consumer, You may have the following rights to Your CA Personal Information: (i) Access. Request access to Your CA Personal Information that We collect, use, disclose, or sell; (ii) _Deletion_. Request deletion of Your CA Personal Information; and (iii) _CA Personal Information Sold or Disclosed For Business Purposes_. Request information about the CA Personal Information We have "sold" (as defined under CCPA) or disclosed for business purposes within the preceding 12 months. Once We receive and confirm Your request, We will disclose to You:
    * The categories of CA Personal Information We collected about You
    * The categories of sources for the CA Personal Information We collected about You
    * Our business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling that CA Personal Information
    * The categories of third parties with whom We share that CA Personal Information
    * The specifics of CA Personal Information We collected about You
    * If we sold Your CA Personal Information or disclosed Your CA Personal Information for a business purpose, We will disclose to You:
        * The categories of CA Personal Information categories sold
        * The categories of CA Personal Information categories disclosed
* To the extent permitted by applicable law, We may be required to retain some of Your CA Personal Information and certain CA Personal Information as strictly necessary in order for Us to fulfill the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.
* **Exercising California consumer rights**. If You are a California resident and Consumer and wish to exercise any of these rights, You may: (a) contact Us as described in this **_Privacy Policy_**, or (b) call the following toll-free number 1-888.399.1995. When submitting Your request, You may be asked to provide certain information, which may include additional proof of identification, so that We can verify Your identity and validate the request. We are not responsible for requests that are not sent or submitted properly, or that do not have complete information. Please note that You are limited by law in the number of requests You may submit per year. We will not discriminate against You by offering You different pricing or products, or by providing You with a different level or quality of products or services, based solely upon You exercising Your rights to Your CA Personal Information. 
* **Do Not Sell My Personal Information**. If We “sell” (as defined by CCPA) Your CA Personal Information to a third party, as a California Resident and Consumer, You have the right to opt-out of the sale of Your CA Personal Information. If You wish to exercise this right, please contact Us as described in this **_Privacy Policy_**, or call the following toll-free number 1-888.399.1995. You have the right to opt-out of the sale of Your personal information. Once We receive and confirm a verifiable California consumer request from You, We will stop selling Your personal information. To exercise Your right to opt-out, please contact Us. Service Providers we partner with (for example, our analytics or advertising partners) may use technology on the Service in a manner that may potentially be considered a sale of CA Personal Information as defined by the CCPA law. If You wish to opt out of the use of Your CA Personal Information for interest-based advertising purposes and these potential sales as defined under CCPA, You may do so by following the instructions below. Please note that any opt out is specific to the browser You use. You may need to opt out on every browser that You use.
    * Website - You can opt out of receiving ads that are personalized as served by our Service Provider partners by following Our instructions presented on the Service and in the section on **_Tracking Technologies and Cookies_** in this Privacy Policy above, and
        * The NAI's opt-out platform: [www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)
        * The EDAA's opt-out platform [www.youronlinechoices.com/](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/)
        * The DAA's opt-out platform: [optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN](http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN)

The opt out will place a cookie on Your computer that is unique to the browser You use to opt out. If you change browsers or delete the cookies saved by your browser, You will need to opt out again.

* **Mobile Devices:** Your mobile device may give You the ability to opt out of the use of information about the apps You use in order to serve You ads that are targeted to Your interests:
    * "Opt out of Interest-Based Ads" or "Opt out of Ads Personalization" on Android devices
    * "Limit Ad Tracking" on iOS devices

You can also stop the collection of location information from Your mobile device by changing the preferences on Your mobile device.

To the extent that You elect to designate an authorized agent to make a request on Your behalf, they must identify that they are contacting Us as agent and will be required to provide appropriate documentation including written signed authorization by You, proof of Your identity, and verification of their identity; or a valid, designated power of attorney as required under the California Probate Code. We may require additional proof of authority or may need to contact You directly to validate the request. If You are under the age of 16, We will not sell Your CA Personal Information without proper consent.

Your request to Us must:

* Provide sufficient information that allows Us to reasonably verify You are the person about whom We collected personal information or an authorized representative.
* Describe Your request with sufficient detail that allows Us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.

We cannot respond to Your request or provide You with the required information if We cannot verify Your identity or authority to make the request and confirm that the personal information relates to You. We will disclose and deliver the required information free of charge within 45 days of receiving Your verifiable request. The time period to provide the required information may be extended by an additional 45 days when reasonably necessary and with prior notice.

If You have questions or concerns regarding Your privacy under this Privacy Policy, please contact Us at [privacy@cambiumlearning.com](mailto:privacy@cambiumlearning.com), or by writing to:

Attention: Privacy

Cambium Intermediate Holdings LLC

17855 Dallas Parkway, Suite 400

Dallas, Texas 75287

Please be sure to note that You are contacting Us regarding this  [www.cambiumlearning.com/](https://www.cambiumlearning.com/) Website Privacy Policy and Your rights as a California Consumer under CCPA.

### "Do Not Track" Policy as Required by California Online Privacy Protection Act (CalOPPA)

Our Service does not respond to Do Not Track signals.

However, some third party websites do keep track of Your browsing activities. If You are visiting such websites, You can set Your preferences in Your web browser to inform websites that You do not want to be tracked. You can enable or disable DNT by visiting the preferences or settings page of Your web browser.

### Your California Privacy Rights (California's Shine the Light law)

Under California Civil Code Section 1798 (California's Shine the Light law), California residents with an established business relationship with us can request information once a year about sharing their Personal Data with third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes.

If You'd like to request more information under the California Shine the Light law, and if You are a California resident, You can contact Us at  [privacy@cambiumlearning.com](mailto:privacy@cambiumlearning.com), or by writing to:

Attention: Privacy

Cambium Intermediate Holdings LLC

17855 Dallas Parkway, Suite 400

Dallas, Texas 75287

### California Privacy Rights for Minor Users (California Business and Professions Code Section 22581)

California Business and Professions Code section 22581 allows California residents under the age of 18 who are registered users of online sites, services or applications to request and obtain removal of content or information they have publicly posted.

To request removal of such data, and if You are a California resident, You can contact Us at  [privacy@cambiumlearning.com](mailto:privacy@cambiumlearning.com), or by writing to:

Attention: Privacy

Cambium Intermediate Holdings LLC

17855 Dallas Parkway, Suite 400

Dallas, Texas 75287

Please be sure to use the email address associated with Your account, and note that you are contacting Us regarding this  [https://www.cambiumlearning.com/](http://httsp//www.cambiumlearning.com/) Website Privacy Policy and Your rights as a California resident under California Code section 22581.

Be aware that Your request does not guarantee complete or comprehensive removal of content or information posted online and that the law may not permit or require removal in certain circumstances.

### Children Under 13

We do not intentionally collect any information on children under 13 years of age from our Website. We will undertake to delete any details of any such users where a parent, guardian or authorized school official has notified Us that any such details have been obtained.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We will review and may update Our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify You of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page with the “Last updated” date indicated at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, You can contact Us at  [privacy@cambiumlearning.com](mailto:privacy@cambiumlearning.com), or by writing to:

Attention: Privacy

Cambium Intermediate Holdings LLC

17855 Dallas Parkway, Suite 400

Dallas, Texas 75287
